Do you still want to bet, Your Highness?
No.
I want to return to Rouran.
What did you say?
The feud between you two brothers has nothing to do with me.
I am now Princess Yu in name.
What does it matter where I am?
Besides, Your Highness has already gotten
what you wanted,
the leverage to fight for the throne.
As for the rest,
I really don't want to be involved anymore.
So, Your Highness,
please send me back to Rouran.
What if I refuse?
People have legs.
I can always walk my own path.
Xiyao.
Don't blame me for being ruthless.
Since you are already my woman,
you can only stay in my Prince Yu's Manor.
Does it hurt?
You can tell me now, right?
What?
What riddle were you and Yuwen Jia playing?
No.
I can't tell Jingxuan the whole truth yet.
I bluffed him.
Think about it.
Yuwen Jia clearly had the chance to strike before,
but he didn't kill me.
There must be a reason why he couldn't.
Oh.
Where is Mr. Su?
Probably went to find Princess Xiyao.
Does it hurt?
No.
What did you say?
You want to return to Prince Yu's Mansion?
I am Princess Yu,
and a princess of Rouran.
I belong in Prince Yu's Mansion.
Xiyao.
I was wrong.
Young Master Su, please behave yourself.
No.
Jingxuan.
Xiyao seems to have been hit by Yuwen Jia's Soul-Destroying Nail.
How dare he!
I didn't expect Prince Yu to be so reckless all of a sudden.
Is there something we don't know?
Our top priority is to rescue Princess Xiyao.
He should be dining at the Empress's palace tonight.
He will return to his mansion around the hour of Xu.
As long as we plan properly,
we can definitely get her back.
There are no buts.
Go prepare quickly.
Yuwen Jia is acting so strangely.
You probably know the inside story, don't you?
Be careful.
Then we'll talk when you get back.
How is it? Are you hurt anywhere?
Oh, I got hit.
Strange, there are no internal injuries.
Hey, I didn't lie to you.
When I came out of Prince Yu's Mansion,
I was hit by Princess Xiyao.
Right, what about the Soul-Destroying Nail in Princess Xiyao's body?
Don't worry.
There's still some antidote left from last time.
I gave it to Aye.
I kept forgetting to ask you before.
How did you
get the antidote from Yuwen Jia?
What?
You don't believe I can beat Yuwen Jia?
Oh, right.
I'll go check on
Princess Xiyao.
Princess Xiyao is fine.
Young Master Su, you can rest assured.
Miss Tang, you are a skilled and kind doctor.
I...
Young Master Su, you don't need to be so polite.
Miss Tang, you came here alone.
Is there something you want to ask?
I was hit by the Soul-Destroying Nail before.
Jingxuan went to Yuwen Jia alone for the antidote.
Did you know about this, Young Master Su?
Don't you already have the answer, Miss Tang?
Yes, it's the Soul Jade.
The Soul Jade recognizes its master.
Normally, it would return on its own within a few days.
But this time...
Rest assured, Miss Tang.
Jingxuan said
the Soul Jade cannot be destroyed by force.
Perhaps he used other means to trap it.
That's right.
Our Rouran tribe
has a family heirloom.
It looks like an ordinary wooden box on the outside,
but it can actually trap anything in the world.
But it's no longer here.
Because Yuwen Jia insisted on having it
as her dowry.
Jingxuan.
Let's go.
Get out.